# Steven Bi

### **Full-Stack Developer**

Perth WA 6107 steven.bb.0221@gmail.com +61 450 980 608

Qualified software engineer, experiences in coding Node.js, Python, passionate about web app development with React/Vue & FastAPI/Django ecosystem, good on web based data visualization, API development and data processing. Familiar with Docker, Git and Postgres dev environment as well as knowledge of AWS/GCP.

Willing to relocate to: Perth WA - -

#### Personal Details

Eligible to work in Australia: Yes

Highest Level of Education: Bachelor Degree

### Work Experience

### **Full Stack Developer**

Pointerra - Perth WA June 2022 to Present

- deployment process for Pointerra's SaaS applications, maintain platform reliability, scalability, and robustness improvements (Vue & Django & Node js & AWS)
- Managing and improving the automated software build and test platform for frontend system

#### **Software Developer**

Atomorphis - Perth WA November 2020 to April 2022

Working on a primary in house product 'Gemini' which is an agent based simulation for helping to identify bottlenecks and plan in mining project , as well as maintain other exist products such as excel & python based data modeling tool.

- Implement Gemini front-end system (React & MUI) from scratch, including interactive geological map base
- Finished & delivered a fully functional Gemini prototype for demo.
- Continuously work on Gemini data visualization of mining fleet and equipment simulation in 2D & 3D animation, onsite / underground.
- API development (FastApi)

• Dockerize and maintain whole front-end sytem in docker container

#### Web developer

South Pacific Union Group - Bunbury WA February 2020 to May 2020

Short contract with a local chain hotel in Bunbury, resolve current hotel website issues as well as maintain IT devices.

- Restore website from the damaged backup & online booking system (Wordpress)
- Excel based data summary tool (Python & Pyxl)
- offlline mail marketing system (Python)

### **Software Developer**

Lianjia (https://sh.lianjia.com/) - Shang Hai March 2019 to October 2019

- Maintain current web app backend (Python & Django)
- Improve UI user experience (Materal UI & React)
- Develop & maintain new features

#### Education

### **Bachelor of Science (Computing) in Software Engineering**

Curtin University - Perth WA

August 2014 to December 2018

#### Skills

- JS & React & Node (3 years)
- Python & API Development (3 years)
- Html & Css (3 years)
- Material UI (3 years)
- Git & Docker (3 years)
- Mapbox & DeckGL (2 years)
- · Postgres (2 years)
- Django & FastApi (2 years)
- Pyxl (1 year)

## Links

https://chen-bbe.github.io/MyPage/

https://github.com/Chen-BBe/

### Certifications and Licenses

## **SCJP**

2010 to 2012

Sun Certified Java Programmer

## Additional Information

• Language: Mandarin and English